<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Game Master Notes on MountHeart</title><link>https://metalblueberry.github.io/MountHeart/master/</link><description>Recent content in Game Master Notes on MountHeart</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>es-es</language><copyright>Game Master</copyright><atom:link href="https://metalblueberry.github.io/MountHeart/master/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Emergencia</title><link>https://metalblueberry.github.io/MountHeart/diario/2021-11-06/</link><pubDate>Sat, 06 Nov 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://metalblueberry.github.io/MountHeart/diario/2021-11-06/</guid><description>&lt;p>Natura y Ohmrom salvan el circo cuando Atlas pierde el control y empieza a atacar al público. Parece que no ha sino un hecho aislado y la ciudad se encuentra en estado de emergencia.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>El circo</title><link>https://metalblueberry.github.io/MountHeart/diario/2021-10-24/</link><pubDate>Sun, 24 Oct 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://metalblueberry.github.io/MountHeart/diario/2021-10-24/</guid><description>&lt;p>Sim, Mon, Natura y Ohmrom visitan el circo Wolpertinger.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title/><link>https://metalblueberry.github.io/MountHeart/personajes/neru/readme/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://metalblueberry.github.io/MountHeart/personajes/neru/readme/</guid><description>&lt;p>source
&lt;a href="https://www.reddit.com/r/DnD/comments/g7r5pm/oc_art_watcher/">https://www.reddit.com/r/DnD/comments/g7r5pm/oc_art_watcher/&lt;/a>&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Abilities</title><link>https://metalblueberry.github.io/MountHeart/personajes/ohmrom/habilidades/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://metalblueberry.github.io/MountHeart/personajes/ohmrom/habilidades/</guid><description>&lt;p>lista de habilidades&lt;/p>
&lt;p>Blood Thirst determines the necessity of blood and affects changes in the abilities you can use. You can safely have the same number of points as your level. Blood Thirst is increased by 1 per day. If you go over your max points, Barkilara will try to drain your blood once per extra point per day. Save CD CHA. You take a Drain blood impact&lt;/p>
&lt;table>
&lt;thead>
&lt;tr>
&lt;th>ability&lt;/th>
&lt;th>description&lt;/th>
&lt;/tr>
&lt;/thead>
&lt;tbody>
&lt;tr>
&lt;td>Drain blood&lt;/td>
&lt;td>You can drink the blood of your enemies. Before an attack, you must awake Barkilara and declare the amount of blood you offer. After a successful hit, you can make extra damage equal to your Blood Thirst points and lose them. If you miss, Barkilara will try to drink your blood Save CD CHA. You can always offer at least 1 blood.&lt;/td>
&lt;/tr>
&lt;tr>
&lt;td>Return blood&lt;/td>
&lt;td>You can ask Barkilara to return blood to your body. declare the amount of blood you want. Heals yourself that number of hit points CHA Persuasion 15. The Thirst is increased by this amount, This can be done as an extra action&lt;/td>
&lt;/tr>
&lt;tr>
&lt;td>Alter body&lt;/td>
&lt;td>You change the shape of your body to match other human creature if you drink their blood. It last between 30m and 1h. You don&amp;rsquo;t receive any benefits apart from the physical change. It takes 1m to transform completely. This action will reduce your blood thirst by 1 when you drink the blood.&lt;/td>
&lt;/tr>
&lt;/tbody>
&lt;/table></description></item><item><title>Abys notes</title><link>https://metalblueberry.github.io/MountHeart/master/abys/abys/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://metalblueberry.github.io/MountHeart/master/abys/abys/</guid><description>&lt;p>Los jugadores van al infierno por accidente al ser asesinados/Al caer por una grieta creada por un ser malvado poderoso llevando una guadaña, scyte de sangre.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>&lt;del>El jugador de Andrei es intercambiado por otra persona buena O al morir estando cerca de laura Aasimar&lt;/del>&lt;/p>
&lt;p>Laura investiga al ser que busca la espada de sangre y por eso se encuentra en la misma ubicación. Ha ido con un miembro de su familia que desprecia a los pobres, mendigos, otras razas&amp;hellip; Han sido enviados buscando eliminar el artefacto por su peligrosidad.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>Andrei podría estar intentando robar joyas, entre las que resulta que se encuentra la piedra de sangre, cuando el miembro de la familia de Laura lo ve, se lo impide y le condena a perder las manos por ladrón. La sangre activa la gema y es cuando aparece el ser malvado que acaba en un instante con la vida de toda la ciudad.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>Laura acompaña al familiar para aprender, es mucho mas fuerte, puede que sepa lanzar conjuros de fuego&lt;/p>
&lt;p>Andre intercambia su cuerpo con el familiar de Laura. Laura eventualmente se da cuenta, y no le parece mal debido a que odiaba a su familiar&lt;/p>
&lt;p>debido a que tienen sangre aasimar, no pueden ser condenados en el infierno, no deberían de estar ahí. Sin embargo, las reglas son claras, nadie puede irse.&lt;/p>
&lt;h2 id="cuando-caen-al-infierno">Cuando caen al infierno,&lt;/h2>
&lt;ul>
&lt;li>
&lt;p>los demonios no saben que es lo que ocurre. Los reciben amablemente como si se tratara de alienigenas.&lt;/p>
&lt;/li>
&lt;li>
&lt;p>No saben que sus cuerpos contienen sangre.&lt;/p>
&lt;/li>
&lt;li>
&lt;p>La sanbre da poder a los demonios.&lt;/p>
&lt;/li>
&lt;li>
&lt;p>Su religion prohibe el uso de la sangre, pero algunos no siguen las leyes e intentan adquirirla de cualquier forma.&lt;/p>
&lt;/li>
&lt;li>
&lt;p>La mayoria nunca ha visto sangre de verdad. es como una leyenda. O que no existe&lt;/p>
&lt;/li>
&lt;li>
&lt;p>Trabajan torturando almas, aunque no todos&lt;/p>
&lt;/li>
&lt;li>
&lt;p>Se tortura buscando que es lo peor que soporta cada alma. Mostrando imágenes inquietantes, soledad, poner música mala, poner en compañia de su peor enemigo&amp;hellip;&lt;/p>
&lt;/li>
&lt;li>
&lt;p>Pueden transferir almas a cuerpos sintéticos para poder infligir mas dolor. Es un avance de la ciencia&lt;/p>
&lt;/li>
&lt;li>
&lt;p>Cobran en monedas de cristal. Es un recursos escaso.&lt;/p>
&lt;/li>
&lt;li>
&lt;p>Se puede encontrar oro y plata utilizado como decoración.&lt;/p>
&lt;/li>
&lt;li>
&lt;p>Los demonios con mucho dinero se entretienen bebiendo y jugando en las tabernas. Algunos de dedican a investigar, otros cazan bestias como método de vida.&lt;/p>
&lt;/li>
&lt;li>
&lt;p>Siempre están buscando formas de torturar mejor a las almas&lt;/p>
&lt;/li>
&lt;li>
&lt;p>Los gritos de agonía producen energía mágica que se puede usar para alimentar artilugios. Steampunk??&lt;/p>
&lt;/li>
&lt;li>
&lt;p>Hay barcos que funcionan con esta energía, se utilizan para viajar entre las distintas ciudades. no hay muchas&lt;/p>
&lt;/li>
&lt;li>
&lt;p>Se alimentan de carne de criaturas que a su vez se alimentan de azufre, Se encuentra fácilmente.&lt;/p>
&lt;/li>
&lt;li>&lt;/li>
&lt;/ul>
&lt;p>El infierno parece una gran ciudad donde viven demonios que trabajan torturando a la gente que ha acabado en el infierno. Cada diablo se especializa en distintos tipos de tortura y hay zonas dedicadas a ello. No a todo el mundo se le tortura igual.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>Las almas se recogen del mar.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>Las afueras de la ciudad son un bosque de arboles secos. Ni siquiera los demonios se atreven a ir mas alla. Creen que hay monstruos que les asustan incluso a ellos. Los monstruos tienen poderes mágicos y de telepatía&lt;/p>
&lt;h1 id="ideas">Ideas&lt;/h1>
&lt;p>Una gema es todo lo que queda al matar a alguien
La sangre llega al rio y vuelven a la vida. Se puede evitar guardando parte de ella.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Anakin</title><link>https://metalblueberry.github.io/MountHeart/master/sidequests/anakin/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://metalblueberry.github.io/MountHeart/master/sidequests/anakin/</guid><description>
&lt;div style="display: flex">
&lt;div style="flex-grow:1">
&lt;div>CHA&lt;/div>
&lt;div>2&lt;/div>
&lt;div>15&lt;/div>
&lt;/div>
&lt;div style="flex-grow:1">
&lt;div>CON&lt;/div>
&lt;div>2&lt;/div>
&lt;div>14&lt;/div>
&lt;/div>
&lt;div style="flex-grow:1">
&lt;div>DEX&lt;/div>
&lt;div>0&lt;/div>
&lt;div>11&lt;/div>
&lt;/div>
&lt;div style="flex-grow:1">
&lt;div>INT&lt;/div>
&lt;div>0&lt;/div>
&lt;div>11&lt;/div>
&lt;/div>
&lt;div style="flex-grow:1">
&lt;div>STR&lt;/div>
&lt;div>3&lt;/div>
&lt;div>16&lt;/div>
&lt;/div>
&lt;div style="flex-grow:1">
&lt;div>WIS&lt;/div>
&lt;div>0&lt;/div>
&lt;div>11&lt;/div>
&lt;/div>
&lt;/div>
&lt;p>&lt;a href="https://www.improved-initiative.com/e/">https://www.improved-initiative.com/e/&lt;/a>&lt;/p>
&lt;p>Anakin is a knignt for the order of &lt;strong>Onir&lt;/strong>. He is looking for a half giant that has been seen on this lands. The plan is to kill it to remove the amenace.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Intro</title><link>https://metalblueberry.github.io/MountHeart/master/intro/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://metalblueberry.github.io/MountHeart/master/intro/</guid><description>&lt;h1 id="this-should-not-be-read-by-players">This should not be read by players!&lt;/h1>
&lt;!--more -->
&lt;h2 id="the-office">The office&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>Sara. as the escape room receptionist, leads the players into a room that looks like an office. A desk is in the middle with a wooden chair. the are 4 lock drawers. On the table there is a book, ink and quill and candles.
The floor is wooden and the walls are stone. There is a window with bars where light comes in.&lt;/p>
&lt;ul>
&lt;li>On the walls there are a 4 oil lamps.&lt;/li>
&lt;li>The door is wood reinforced with metal and it is closed and locked. It can be unlocked by manually moving a barrel.&lt;/li>
&lt;li>There is a coat rack with a light coat. it is brown with a two pockets and a symbol of a red 8 pointed start over a black circle. In one of the pockets there is a knife.&lt;/li>
&lt;li>There are two wall decorations with the same symbol. One is hiding the door where you came in.&lt;/li>
&lt;li>There is a closed vault.&lt;/li>
&lt;/ul>
&lt;p>Through the window it can be seen a forest with a kind of tree that they do not recognise.&lt;/p>
&lt;h2 id="the-corridor">The corridor&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>There is a corridor with 3 doors on one side, you are in the 2th floor on the left of the corridor. There is a double door on each end. There are decorations on the walls with the red star over black.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>One of the doors leads to the exterior and is closed. It has an small window to look through&lt;/p>
&lt;p>The other door leads to the cells&lt;/p>
&lt;blockquote>
&lt;p>Event, an officer exits his room and finds the players. Asks them what are they doing here.
Event, one of the doors is open and contains similar items&lt;/p>
&lt;/blockquote>
&lt;h2 id="the-cells-compounds">The cells compounds&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>There are two floors, You are on the 2nd floor. there is a circular path around a hole protected with bars that prevent anyone from climbing out, it is about 10m depth. There is a manual elevator on one side. There is an armed big guy next to the elevator. He carries a club and wears a leather clothes.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>On the 1st floor there is a rock floor and about 10 people, some of them naked and others wearing ragged clothes.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>There are another 6 compounds similar to this one connected by 10m corridors&lt;/p>
&lt;p>There are 12 stupid guards, one per compound. and 3 officers.&lt;/p>
&lt;blockquote>
&lt;p>Event: prisoners fight.&lt;/p>
&lt;/blockquote>
&lt;h2 id="exterior">Exterior&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>On the jail is carved into a wall of a stone mountain and the only exit is the door in the corridor.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>There is a barn with 4 horses and a carriage prepared to transport up to 6 prisoners.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Onir</title><link>https://metalblueberry.github.io/MountHeart/master/onir/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://metalblueberry.github.io/MountHeart/master/onir/</guid><description>&lt;p>Onir is the god of justice. His knights are famous for being helpful and watching for the people in the Alzian republic. The prince has been using his influence in his favour making people believe that other species are dangerous.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>Coronel Adrian is the one responsible of tweaking the Onir&amp;rsquo;s knights behaviour.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Sound</title><link>https://metalblueberry.github.io/MountHeart/lore/sound/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://metalblueberry.github.io/MountHeart/lore/sound/</guid><description>&lt;p>Sound effects for the game&lt;/p>
&lt;!-- more-->
&lt;h2 id="base-ambient">Base Ambient&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>&lt;iframe width="100%"
src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/FKRLBwiP_Qo"
frameborder="0"
allow="clipboard-write; encrypted-media"
>&lt;/iframe>
&lt;iframe width="100%"
src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/nRe3xFeyhVY"
frameborder="0"
allow="clipboard-write; encrypted-media"
>&lt;/iframe>
&lt;iframe width="100%"
src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/K1JvqHnSHfc"
frameborder="0"
allow="clipboard-write; encrypted-media"
>&lt;/iframe>
&lt;iframe width="100%"
src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/aK4JSwhdcdE"
frameborder="0"
allow="clipboard-write; encrypted-media"
>&lt;/iframe>
&lt;iframe width="100%"
src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/dd10InDdvJE"
frameborder="0"
allow="clipboard-write; encrypted-media"
>&lt;/iframe>&lt;/p>
&lt;h2 id="extra-ambient">Extra Ambient&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>city
&lt;iframe width="100%"
src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/RO0tlWeoUmc"
frameborder="0"
allow="clipboard-write; encrypted-media"
>&lt;/iframe>
river
&lt;iframe width="100%"
src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/IvjMgVS6kng"
frameborder="0"
allow="clipboard-write; encrypted-media"
>&lt;/iframe>
waterfal
&lt;iframe width="100%"
src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/HchoJcYNYlU"
frameborder="0"
allow="clipboard-write; encrypted-media"
>&lt;/iframe>
waves
&lt;iframe width="100%"
src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/btmjDyff6E8"
frameborder="0"
allow="clipboard-write; encrypted-media"
>&lt;/iframe>
forest
&lt;iframe width="100%"
src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/xNN7iTA57jM"
frameborder="0"
allow="clipboard-write; encrypted-media"
>&lt;/iframe>
fire
&lt;iframe width="100%"
src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/UgHKb_7884o"
frameborder="0"
allow="clipboard-write; encrypted-media"
>&lt;/iframe>&lt;/p>
&lt;h2 id="weather">Weather&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>thunder
&lt;iframe width="100%"
src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/qOHuT5njtRA"
frameborder="0"
allow="clipboard-write; encrypted-media"
>&lt;/iframe>
rain
&lt;iframe width="100%"
src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/q76bMs-NwRk"
frameborder="0"
allow="clipboard-write; encrypted-media"
>&lt;/iframe>&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Taiga</title><link>https://metalblueberry.github.io/MountHeart/lore/locations/taiga/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://metalblueberry.github.io/MountHeart/lore/locations/taiga/</guid><description>&lt;p>&lt;p class="md__image">
&lt;a href="taiga.jpg">
&lt;img src="taiga.jpg" alt="fauna" />
&lt;/a>
&lt;/p>&lt;/p>
&lt;p>&lt;a href="https://www.bioenciclopedia.com/taiga/">https://www.bioenciclopedia.com/taiga/&lt;/a>&lt;/p></description></item></channel></rss>